I, Renato di Rubini, first prince
of the Kingdom of Rubini,
hereby call off our engagement.
It began with a sudden end
to an engagement.
Episode 1
How I Searched For A Promising Catch
Kingdom of Rubini Royal Capital
Duke Annovazzi's carriage has arrived.
Mimi!
Aida!
It's been so long!
You seem well, Mimi.
Has it been two years?
I'm so glad to see you.
SHAKE
Duke Ametis! Thank you
for agreeing to be my guardian!
My father sends his regards as well!
W-Welcome to the Ametis
family home, Lady Maria.
Yes, sir!
Milady!
Excuse me, Your Grace.
Don't worry about it, Lady Maria.
Your magnanimous personality
has saved Aida countless times.
Is that right?
I hope you'll continue to be friends.
That said, Aida is no longer
merely my daughter.
I ask that you use your discretion.
You can't suddenly take her
to faraway places like you once did.
This is the Kingdom of Rubini, Father.
We can't do what we did back in the
Kingdom of Muro where Mimi's from.
I'm just worried about you, Aida.
You'll become a royal soon.
Please, Father.
BLAZE
You can count on me, Your Grace!
I'll protect Aida with all my might!
Ah, I have an audience
with His Majesty now.
Lady Maria, please make yourself at home.
Aida, I leave the rest in your hands.
She screwed up already...
I'm sorry my father
was rude to you, Mimi.
It's totally fine.
More importantly, Aida, didn't you
get engaged to the Prince of Rubini?
What's he like? How'd you meet?
Aw, shucks.
Our families may be distantly
related, but I'm still proud of you.
I knew you could do it, Aida.
My father forced it to happen.
What?! Then how do you feel?
I'm very honored, of course.
I'm sure I'd pay dearly if I refused.
Anyway, I'd rather hear about you.
Why did you suddenly
decide to study abroad?
Don't you need to look after your family?
Don't they need you?
Aida, I'm here to find a promising catch.
A promising catch?
I believe I told you in my letter...
One, two, three! One—
RUMBLE
Milady! Lady Mimi!
A young master's been born.
You have a younger brother.
A younger brother?
Mimi, this is your younger brother.
He's so soft and warm.
F-Fantastic! I have an heir!
Mimi, go find a husband.
The most promising one you can find.
find... find... find...
I don't believe it. I had no idea.
I'm so sorry.
Sorry? Why are you sorry?
Because you've worked so hard
to become the Annovazzi family heir.
Your studies, practice, and training...
You've learned so many things
a lady normally wouldn't need to.
Oh, I'd hardly call them unnecessary.
They're all useful life skills
even if I'm not the heir.
What?
A male heir is preferred, but my
parents only had girls until recently.
I just happen to be one of them.
You make it sound so simple.
Because my dream isn't to
take over the Annovazzi family.
Nothing would please me more than
Teo becoming a marvelous heir.
What could be better
than everyone finding joy?
That sounds very like you, Mimi.
His freeloading big sister
can't hang around forever.
So I have to find a promising catch.
You're not looking in your local area?
I already did!
But all the suitable matches were taken.
Maybe I'm just not very popular.
I wouldn't say that.
I spoke my mind again!
That's a bad habit of yours.
Anyway, that's why I'm here studying
abroad to find a promising catch.
I hope you find someone nice.
I should show you around
the royal academy first.
Yes, please.
This was originally a school
exclusively for royals.
But two generations ago,
the king decided it would be best
if they studied alongside nobles
and began admitting them.
It's good for nobles to get to
know each other from a young age.
I see.
Everyone's so polite. Is it because
you're engaged to the prince?
Maybe not.
Hey, Aida. Is that a transfer student?
Yes, she is. Let me introduce you.
This is Maria Annovazzi. This is—
Nice to meet you. Call me Mimi.
The prince...
The prince?!
So, His Highness?
Call me Placido.
I see. So you're Mimi.
I'm delighted to meet you.
Aida's told me all about you.
What? Really?
I told him you're my best friend.
Your family hosted Aida to help
with her asthma, didn't they?
I heard she wasn't sure if you
were a boy or girl at first.
Your Highness!
That's right.
I didn't know how to
wear dresses back then.
In fact, I still struggle with them today.
Mimi!
Truly, you exceed my expectations.
No wonder you're Aida's friend.
What? Uh...
I know what I'm like, but Aida is
the most ladylike of all ladies.
Is that right?
BONK BONK
At first, Aida threw chestnuts at me.
Stay away from me! Don't touch me!
She didn't even remove the husks.
What? No way.
That's because you teased me
about being a greedy glutton.
Not to mention that was
more than ten years ago.
I'm surprised. I thought
Aida was a natural-born lady.
Please, no more.
So that's how it is.
I understand your
situation and goals now.
I'll find some promising
young lords for you.
Really? Thank you.
Brother!
Did he not hear me?
Give me a minute.
I don't think Prince Renato will come.
No luck.
I wanted to introduce Mimi,
but he said he had work to do.
He seems busier than ever recently.
Well, my brother's far more talented
than me, but he can be a bit inflexible.
He's a perfectionist and workaholic.
His aide, Raimondo, asked me
to help my brother, so I'm off.
See you later, Aida and Mimi.
Have you seen enough of the academy?
You bet!
I'm sorry.
Shame on you for making a ruckus here!
Please forgive her, Lady Eleonora.
I offer my apologies as well.
I can't reject an apology from
the fiancée of the Prince of Rubini.
That would make me the bad guy.
Do be careful from now on.
What unbelievable strength...
Don't mind her.
Lady Eleonora just
speaks that way sometimes.
Right. She seemed reluctant,
but she did forgive me.
Aida seems friendly with Prince Placido,
but he's not her fiancé.
That must mean she's engaged to
his older brother, Prince Renato.
But she doesn't seem happy about it.
I need to find my own promising catch.
Always a Catch!
I'll do my best.
How are you, Father and Mother?
I've been studying abroad
for two months, and I feel great.
Aida treats me well,
and I've made friends.
How do you do, Lady Annovazzi?
I heard you're staying
with Duke Ametis's family.
Are you free today, milady?
Where is Lady Aida today?
I'm sure they're great people.
I need more time to find a fiancé.
Oh? Mimi?
Prince Placido.
Where's Aida? She's not with you?
She's had a fever since last night.
It's a shame, but she's
skipping the party.
I see. I'm worried about her.
Right? I'm sure you're
very worried about her.
O-Of course I am.
Um...
Lady Maria Annovazzi.
Would you honor me,
Placido di Rubini, with a dance?
What?! But I'm not used to dancing yet.
I'd only cause you trouble.
It's all right. The important thing
is that you have fun.
Yes, Your Highness.
This is it!
I'm hungry after that workout.
Aida is lucky to have a friend like you.
I believe Aida went to stay
with you in the first place
because she exhausted herself
studying to be ladylike.
It's probably the reason
for today's absence as well.
That's news to me.
Aida's always been
a perfectly put together lady.
I think you're helping Aida
a lot just by being with her.
Yes, Your Majesty. I'll protect Aida.
That's encouraging.
Perhaps she'll recover if they
formally announce their engagement
at the graduation party.
Graduation party?
The students one year
above us are graduating.
Prince Renato will be the center
of attention this year.
The remaining students
are also allowed to attend.
I bet it's a luxurious party.
Today's party was amazing, too.
All the steak you can eat.
That's great.
Also, Prince Placido is really nice.
He really is.
Hey, Aida, do you...
Uh, nothing.
All right! I'll work hard
to find a fiancé at the party!
You'll need to control your
habit of speaking your mind.
I'll be careful.
While learning to be ladylike with Aida,
I wait for Prince Placido
to introduce me to someone.
Teo, make sure you listen to Father,
Mother, and your older sisters.
Take care.
There.
Are you ready?
Your hair glitters
like autumn wheat, Mimi.
It's not as smooth or glossy
as your blonde hair, Aida.
It's, uh, a beautiful golden...
gold color.
Thank you. We'll work on your language
skills when we get back from the party.
Okay, that should do it. Let's go.
You don't need to ride
with Prince Renato?
Isn't he your fiancé?
He's a very busy man.
I see. I guess he is a prince.
If it were me, I'd kick
down the door to see him.
Oh, Mimi.
What's wrong?
That's Lady Eleonora's carriage.
Eleonora? Oh, the girl I bumped into.
Lady Eleonora, what
seems to be the problem?
Ugh! Leave me alone.
If your carriage is damaged—
SNEAK
Didn't you hear me?
I don't need your help.
Aida...
My apologies. If you'll excuse us.
I wonder if that carriage will be okay.
That's what I like about you, Mimi.
Huh?
Well, I like how you never
speak poorly of anyone.
Thank you.
Look at all these people.
Isn't that the minister
of the Kingdom of Kihaus?
Even he's attending this party?
Your father's here, too.
Announcing First Prince Renato
and Second Prince Placido.
SWOON
He's always so beautiful.
After graduation, he'll be declared
crown prince, won't he?
Even his furrowed brow is beautiful.
Prince Placido is charming as well.
Why is Prince Renato escorting
someone other than his fiancée?
You're not having him
escort you, Lady Aida?
Lady Eleonora is with him again.
And he's ignoring his fiancée.
I heard your relationship with
Prince Renato is not going well.
You poor thing.
You can talk to me
if there's anything on your mind.
Aida, I'm thirsty.
Let's go to the garden and drink our fill.
But we had more questions.
Thank you, Mimi.
I can't believe they'd ask
those insensitive questions.
They can't call themselves ladies.
Oh, Mimi.
Everyone's interested in Prince Renato.
That means they're
interested in me as well.
But isn't it exhausting not knowing
if they actually care about you or not?
Sometimes.
Well, I only speak the truth,
so don't worry.
You should work on your phrasing, Mimi.
Yes, ma'am.
Prince Renato?
He's escorting Lady Eleonora?
What's going on?
I heard she had trouble with her carriage.
His Highness gave her a ride.
But she shooed away Aida.
What's her angle?
Our eyes met?
He's coming over here.
Mimi.
If you were watching,
that makes things simple.
Lady Aida Ametis.
I, Renato di Rubini, first prince
of the Kingdom of Rubini,
hereby call off our engagement.
Why is this prince telling me
he's calling off his engagement to Aida?
Brother, what's going on?
You've been fooled, Placido.
She's jealous of my relationship
with Lady Eleonora
and has been following her around
and committing violence against her.
Your Highness, that's not her.
I won't allow someone to use their
status to look down on others!
Please calm down, Brother.
Aida isn't that kind of woman.
Unfortunately, Placido,
my aide has gathered evidence.
PANIC
You can't talk your way out of this.
I command you to withdraw
from the academy immediately
and apologize to
Lady Eleonora here and now.
What's going on?
He called off their engagement?
What does that mean?
What am I supposed to do now?
Aida...
BLAZE
I'll protect Aida with all my might!
I told him you're my best friend.
Your Highness!
Do you understand what you're doing?
O-Of course I do.
No, you understand nothing!
My name is Maria Annovazzi!
Your fiancée, Lady Aida Ametis,
is over here!
The first thing you should do is...
buy some glasses!
What?
Translation: Sho Stifler
Timing: Mariana Martinez
Editing: Alicia Ashby
Quality Control: Ashley Barboza
Final Quality Control: Michelle Tymon
BONK BONK BONK
My name is Maria Annovazzi. Call me Mimi.
How do you get Mimi from Maria?
That's not a secret I can reveal here.
Next Time
How I Caught the One That Got Away
Oh, no! I said that out loud again!